Chibarts.
ちばーつ
Hello.
こんにちは
I'm sorry.
すましてますね
Sailor uniform with twin tails...
セイラー服にツインテールが...
Are you okay?
大丈夫か?
Will it pass the inspection?
審査通りますかね?
Eh, are you okay?
え、大丈夫なの?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
J...JS?
Isn't it JS?
JSじゃないか?
What about junior high school students?
中学生はなんだ?
JC?
JD...
J...
It's cute today too.
可愛 いですね、今日も
How was it?
どうでした?
The sex before this.
この前のセクスは
It was good.
良かったです
it was good?
良 かった?
It's a little bit, it's a small pussy,
ちょっとね、小さいマンコなんで、
It was quite difficult to get into it though.
なかなかチンチンが入りづらかったですけど
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Isn't it broken?
壊れてない?
Yeah, somehow.
うん、何とか
Somehow I endured.
何とか耐え
Endure it and don't even recognize it?
耐えて、認識もしてない?
i don't know!
知らない!
It was okay.
大丈夫だった
大丈夫 だ った
If you go outside in large quantities.
外に大量に出ちゃったらね
It's a waste, so I'll put the sperm back next time.
もったいないから、今度、精子戻しますね
There is an A-con.
Aコンいますね
Wow, it's bright.
すごい、明るいね
Well, please give me creampie sex again today.
じゃあ、今日も中出しセクスお願いします
please.
お願いします
Would you like to do a little piledriver?
ちょっとまんぐり返ししますか
water?
水?
Bring some water.
水持ってね
Maika-chan does it all the time.
まいかちゃん、いつもやってる
You like phone calls, right?
電話好きなんでしょう?
I like phone calls.
電話好き
Please masturbate as you like.
好きにオナにしてください
Yes.
はーい
Spread your pussy a little.
ちょっとマンコ広げて
It makes me tremble.
中震わせるね
Kuri-chan, do it.
クリちゃんやって
Push it out.
押し出して
Well then, here.
じゃあ、こっちで
Maika enters.
まいかが入れます
good?
いい?
Okay.
いいよ
It seems like you like chicken.
チキン好きだそうですね
It's big.
大きいよ
I'm going in.
入っちゃう
Come forward.
前に来て
Hands on before.
前に手ついて
Just a little more?
もうちょいか
About the bed.
ベッドについて
yes.
はい
In my sleeping bag.
寝バックで
yes.
はい
Maiko-chan, put the chicken in yourself.
まいこちゃん、チキン自分で入れて
Does it feel good when it goes all the way inside?
奥まで入っちゃうと気持ちいいの?
So yes.
だからそう
I think I'll put this out.
これで出しちゃおうかなって
Okay.
いいよ
Maiko-chan's pussy is narrow, isn't it?
狭いよね、まいこちゃんのマンコね
Yeah.
うん
Should I put it out?
出しちゃおうかな
Maiko-chan's pussy is delicious.
うまいよね、まいこちゃんのマンコね
Are you going to spread it yourself?
自 分で広げちゃうの?
Yeah.
うん
Where should I put it out?
どこに出すの?
You can take it out again.
また入れ出していいよ
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
Chan-chan.
ちゃんちゃん
It would be a waste to give it away.
出 すのもったいないこと
too good to waste.
も ったいない
A lot came out.
いっぱい出てきた
Just give it a try.
ちょっとさっき、 ごぐわりしてみて
A lot will come out of mom.
マ マからいっぱい出るから
Oh, that's true.
あ、ほんとだ
It started trickling down like fireworks.
先行花火みたいにポタポタしてきた
It came out.
出てきちゃったね
It's still coming out.
まだ出てきてるね
Are you out?
出てる?
I've gained weight.
体量出ましたんで
Are you satisfied?
満足しました?
Looks like there's still plenty of time.
まだ余裕そうですね
I can't afford it.
余裕じゃないよ
real?
ほんと?
Should I bring my husband or something?
大夫さんとか連れてきたほうがいい?
Do you like your uncle's father?
おじさんの父がいい?
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing.
すごいね
It was fun sex.
楽しいセックスでしたね